i don't from a city where the white
dudes either do meth or they work
plumbing you know what i mean
but they do something
i never seen so many able-bodied white
dudes just sleeping on the street you
know
and i really hate it when they would ask
me for money you know what i mean like
i'm a black lesbian i'm never going to
give you
[Music]
damn girlfriend my first girlfriend
hughes deal
because i didn't even know how gay i was
to admit this girl you know
i don't know because women we teeter we
do we play games you kiss a girl in the
club to make your boyfriend's dick card
you do silly
you're not always just laying over there
you know what i mean so i didn't know i
was like maybe i'm just grab titties in
the club gay
and not go down on a chick gay very
different gays
very different gays on the spectrum
but i met this girl's like nah man i'm
going down on this chick i'm ready
huge deal man i was scared i had to get
myself charged up to do it
john madden in the huddle like i'm gonna
eat this go go go
god dude i was looking in the mirror
like you are a champion don't worry
and then i got her home and she lay down
on the bed and i realized i had never
seen a vagina from this person
like i've seen mine from this
perspective
i ain't never seen it like that i was
not ready at all i was like oh what the
hell is that
started poking at it like
close your legs let's go to church we
need to pray
you know go ahead pray this gay away
girl we are living foul
but that's the journey you go through
the ups and downs that's how you find
where you're supposed to land you know
what i mean
and i love my wife i do is you know
she's here and i love her
she's supportive but it's hard she
doesn't say a lot of things i care about
i didn't know that was going to be a
problem when i met she talks a lot but i
don't give a about
most of it most of this is like i don't
buy you know and i gotta fein interest
she knows when i'm faced
it's terrible man and i wish she was
there i wish she was saying things that
were more valuable to me
i really do i wish she had more valuable
things and it's like i know as feminists
as women were like yeah everything we
say is
our thought it's like yeah her thoughts
are valuable
but the that's actually coming out
her mouth garbage
pure garbage
[Applause]
this is not good stuff
this is pointless man it's never in the
clutch stuff
it's never things that are gonna save my
life in the moment it's never like we're
driving over a bridge and she's like hey
hon crack those windows
just in case we go off this bridge
laying in this water you'll be able to
open the door do the pressure swim right
out save your life
never information like that never solid
it's always just like i'm in the
kitchen pouring a soda
she strolls by um that's a wine glass
soda doesn't go in there like shut the
up
maybe i want to drink my soda like a
king today out of a goblet
i got my own plans mine your business
what's up bro
how are you though my girl gets all my
nerves you know
i love her but she's annoying
dude that's just like eventually
everybody gets irritated you can't do
anything about it
i started to learn too much about it i
don't like it she's easily
sensationalized she just jumps on
bandwagons i hate that like
she'll read an article and then she's
like i'm a vegan muslim now like that's
not how it works
she's a fake vegan too and that pisses
me off she's not a real vegan it's not
genuine it's not in her heart it's not
about the animals
she just wants to lose weight that's not
a real reason that's trash yeah
it's like the get slim teas weren't
working so now she's a vegan
shut up i watched her eat
vegan burger from white castle and now i
hate her guts
she got a vegan burger from white house
you understand her vegan diet has
inconvenienced me several times i can't
go here
this can't touch this and then she ate a
vegan burger from white castle
if you don't know what a white castle is
just imagine a crack house with a window
on the side
with a crackhead in that just
chucking out sliders
that's a white castle and she
ordered a vegan burger from this place
as if they didn't dip it in pork belly
fat before they gave it to her
then she ate it in my face and wants my
respect like what
it's dope to be back in l.a man i've
been on the road so this is nice it's
nice to just
take all this la and all these
white faces in
because i moved here from boston you
know so when i got to la it was a super
culture shock
i never seen so many homeless white men
in my life it was weird to me
i don't from a city where the white
dudes either do meth or they work
plumbing you know what i mean
but they do something
i never seen so many able-bodied white
dudes just sleeping on the street you
know
and i really hated when they would ask
me for money you know what i mean like
i'm a black lesbian i'm never gonna give
you
go cut your hair and work at a subway
the hell is your problem well that's
what the road does it just
opens you up man exposes you to all
different types of people
i was like la is bad with the homeless
white dudes and then i went to portland
and i was like holy
this is crazy and then i went to
barnaroo and was really mind blown man
i went to tennessee did bonnaroo i'd
never been to a music festival like that
so open and free
just girls walking around with their
titties out everywhere
eating medium rare burgers all
willy-nilly
living i had a medium rare burger myself
the whole time i felt like i was
disrespecting my mother
i was like man you were raised so much
better than this what are you doing
but it was good i liked the texture the
flavor and that's how i ended up trying
mushrooms because i was like it
maybe everything is a lie you know what
i mean
cause i'm a dear kid man i'm scared of
drugs i grew up scared of drugs i didn't
start smoking weeds i was 25 petrified
drugs
never tried mushrooms have arguments
with my friends over not trying
mushrooms
i mean one time my homeboy was like sam
have you never tried mushrooms it's one
of the best drugs on earth
what is your problem have you never
experienced this and i was like dude
all i could think about is going out my
door and seeing a crackhead
and a fiend fighting over a baby
stroller
like i don't live in a mushroom friendly
environment
but it's not like that you know what i'm
saying i did mushrooms i did mushrooms
in bonnaroo man and i took it in a
chocolate bar you know what i'm saying
he gave me a chocolate bar full of
mushrooms because white people know how
to do drugs i ate
and i'm bouncing to this edm band and
they're partying humping off the molly
i'm trying to figure out what's going on
here
and this black dude comes walking
through and he's jacked as jack
super diesel no shirt on looking tough
as
but he's got on these giant fairy wings
but he's still tough he's still bullying
through the crowd with these fairy wings
like
you better not crumple up my furry
wings
i'ma you up
and he walks to this clearing i'm like
holy
and then this dude just this big white
dude just as big in a teletubby costume
walks up to him this is jack
and i'm like what kind of pokemon
showdown is this
about to be and then they hugged each
other
and as i was watching it i was like i
don't know if this is how martin luther
king dreamed it
but this is it this is equality white
dudes what the hell they complaining
about
let me tune in and i'm like them
man they ain't lose
and they don't always get to this point
in their rhetoric where they talk about
they lose losing the country i'd be so
upset
we're losing we're losing what the hell
did they lose we're losing what the hell
did they lose
and then i watched three seasons of
madmen on netflix holy
they lost everything they lost
everything
because at some point that was really
their life
that's what no one understands like we
can't think about it because we never
lived it
that was their life every day they could
wake up in the morning
bourbon on their breath another woman
smell all over their body
walk downstairs kiss their wife in the
mouth she says nothing
just serves on the pancakes with the
perfect butter square in the middle like
an angelima box
it's perfect pancakes they hearty like a
man should you know
jump in their american-made cadillac
swerve all the way to work
swirl go away they get to work run
upstairs secretary greets them with
double d tits they have sex with her
right there in the middle of the office
just put a dick out there white man in
america why would you hesitate
as soon as you're done having sex with
her she says she's pregnant you fire her
you're fired get out of here
who the hell told you to get knocked up
you
go in your office sleep off your
hangover wake up go to a business lunch
get drunk again and get a promotion and
that's what they did every day
that was like their life no
interruptions
and then like women started thinking and
black people wanted to eat sandwiches
next to them and all went to
they lost everything that's why they
don't want mexicans to vote it's a
slippery slope man
you